[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "cat",
        "trueAnswer": "egg",
        "falseAnswer": ["avocado", "onion"]
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "cat",
        "trueAnswer": "carrot",
        "falseAnswer": ["garlic", "chocolate"]
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "cat",
        "trueAnswer": "pumpkin",
        "falseAnswer": ["grapes", "milk"]
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "cat",
        "trueAnswer": "meat",
        "falseAnswer": ["tomato", "deer"]
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "cat",
        "trueAnswer": "chicken",
        "falseAnswer": ["avocado", "potato"]
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "dog",
        "trueAnswer": "egg",
        "falseAnswer": ["avocado", "chocolate"]
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "dog",
        "trueAnswer": "rice",
        "falseAnswer": ["grapes", "onion"]
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "dog",
        "trueAnswer": "meat",
        "falseAnswer": ["garlic", "onion"]
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "dog",
        "trueAnswer": "carrot",
        "falseAnswer": ["eggplant", "garlic"]
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "dog",
        "trueAnswer": "apple",
        "falseAnswer": ["chocolate", "grapes"]
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "cow",
        "trueAnswer": "grass",
        "falseAnswer": ["chocolate", "garlic"]
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "cow",
        "trueAnswer": "hay",
        "falseAnswer": ["orange", "fish"]
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "cow",
        "trueAnswer": "carrot",
        "falseAnswer": ["meat", "cabbage"]
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "cow",
        "trueAnswer": "pumpkin",
        "falseAnswer": ["avocado", "nuts"]
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "cow",
        "trueAnswer": "watermelon",
        "falseAnswer": ["nuts", "cherry"]
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "sheep",
        "trueAnswer": "grass",
        "falseAnswer": ["nuts", "onion"]
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "sheep",
        "trueAnswer": "carrot",
        "falseAnswer": ["garlic", "tomato"]
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "sheep",
        "trueAnswer": "pumpkin",
        "falseAnswer": ["chicken", "eggplant"]
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "sheep",
        "trueAnswer": "apple",
        "falseAnswer": ["meat", "cherry"]
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "sheep",
        "trueAnswer": "pear",
        "falseAnswer": ["avocado", "fish"]
    },
    {
        "id": 21,
        "question": "pig",
        "trueAnswer": "corn",
        "falseAnswer": ["grapes", "pomegranate"]
    },
    {
        "id": 22,
        "question": "pig",
        "trueAnswer": "cabbage",
        "falseAnswer": ["garlic", "eggplant"]
    },
    {
        "id": 23,
        "question": "pig",
        "trueAnswer": "apple",
        "falseAnswer": ["chocolate", "onion"]
    },
    {
        "id": 24,
        "question": "pig",
        "trueAnswer": "pear",
        "falseAnswer": ["nuts", "broccoli"]
    },
    {
        "id": 25,
        "question": "pig",
        "trueAnswer": "pumpkin",
        "falseAnswer": ["orange", "avocado"]
    },
    {
        "id": 26,
        "question": "rabbit",
        "trueAnswer": "carrot",
        "falseAnswer": ["potato", "radish"]
    },
    {
        "id": 27,
        "question": "rabbit",
        "trueAnswer": "cabbage",
        "falseAnswer": ["garlic", "eggplant"]
    },
    {
        "id": 28,
        "question": "rabbit",
        "trueAnswer": "apple",
        "falseAnswer": ["grapes", "onion"]
    },
    {
        "id": 29,
        "question": "rabbit",
        "trueAnswer": "strawberry",
        "falseAnswer": ["pomegranate", "meat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 30,
        "question": "rabbit",
        "trueAnswer": "watermelon",
        "falseAnswer": ["bread", "avocado"]
    },
    {
        "id": 31,
        "question": "horse",
        "trueAnswer": "carrot",
        "falseAnswer": ["potato", "fish"]
    },
    {
        "id": 32,
        "question": "horse",
        "trueAnswer": "grass",
        "falseAnswer": ["garlic", "eggplant"]
    },
    {
        "id": 33,
        "question": "horse",
        "trueAnswer": "apple",
        "falseAnswer": ["grapes", "onion"]
    },
    {
        "id": 34,
        "question": "horse",
        "trueAnswer": "pear",
        "falseAnswer": ["chocolate", "broccoli"]
    },
    {
        "id": 35,
        "question": "horse",
        "trueAnswer": "cucumber",
        "falseAnswer": ["bread", "avocado"]
    },
    {
        "id": 36,
        "question": "donkey",
        "trueAnswer": "leaves",
        "falseAnswer": ["potato", "fish"]
    },
    {
        "id": 37,
        "question": "donkey",
        "trueAnswer": "grass",
        "falseAnswer": ["tomato", "chocolate"]
    },
    {
        "id": 38,
        "question": "donkey",
        "trueAnswer": "apple",
        "falseAnswer": ["olives", "onion"]
    },
    {
        "id": 39,
        "question": "donkey",
        "trueAnswer": "pear",
        "falseAnswer": ["eggplant", "garlic"]
    },
    {
        "id": 40,
        "question": "donkey",
        "trueAnswer": "grass",
        "falseAnswer": ["nuts", "avocado"]
    },
    {
        "id": 41,
        "question": "chicken",
        "trueAnswer": "corn",
        "falseAnswer": ["potato", "fish"]
    },
    {
        "id": 42,
        "question": "chicken",
        "trueAnswer": "carrot",
        "falseAnswer": ["avocado", "chocolate"]
    },
    {
        "id": 43,
        "question": "chicken",
        "trueAnswer": "cucumber",
        "falseAnswer": ["eggplant", "onion"]
    },
    {
        "id": 44,
        "question": "chicken",
        "trueAnswer": "watermelon",
        "falseAnswer": ["grapes", "garlic"]
    },
    {
        "id": 45,
        "question": "chicken",
        "trueAnswer": "cabbage",
        "falseAnswer": ["chocolate", "avocado"]
    },
    {
        "id": 46,
        "question": "duck",
        "trueAnswer": "corn",
        "falseAnswer": ["potato", "fish"]
    },
    {
        "id": 47,
        "question": "duck",
        "trueAnswer": "grass",
        "falseAnswer": ["avocado", "bread"]
    },
    {
        "id": 48,
        "question": "duck",
        "trueAnswer": "rice",
        "falseAnswer": ["eggplant", "onion"]
    },
    {
        "id": 49,
        "question": "duck",
        "trueAnswer": "cabbage",
        "falseAnswer": ["grapes", "garlic"]
    },
    {
        "id": 50,
        "question": "duck",
        "trueAnswer": "cucumber",
        "falseAnswer": ["chocolate", "avocado"]
    },
    {
        "id": 51,
        "question": "goose",
        "trueAnswer": "pear",
        "falseAnswer": ["potato", "meat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 52,
        "question": "goose",
        "trueAnswer": "grass",
        "falseAnswer": ["avocado", "radish"]
    },
    {
        "id": 53,
        "question": "goose",
        "trueAnswer": "pumpkin",
        "falseAnswer": ["eggplant", "onion"]
    },
    {
        "id": 54,
        "question": "goose",
        "trueAnswer": "watermelon",
        "falseAnswer": ["nuts", "garlic"]
    },
    {
        "id": 55,
        "question": "goose",
        "trueAnswer": "cucumber",
        "falseAnswer": ["chocolate", "avocado"]
    },
    {
        "id": 56,
        "question": "goat",
        "trueAnswer": "hay",
        "falseAnswer": ["bread", "meat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 57,
        "question": "goat",
        "trueAnswer": "carrot",
        "falseAnswer": ["avocado", "deer"]
    },
    {
        "id": 58,
        "question": "goat",
        "trueAnswer": "cabbage",
        "falseAnswer": ["grapes", "onion"]
    },
    {
        "id": 59,
        "question": "goat",
        "trueAnswer": "apple",
        "falseAnswer": ["nuts", "garlic"]
    },
    {
        "id": 60,
        "question": "goat",
        "trueAnswer": "cucumber",
        "falseAnswer": ["chocolate", "avocado"]
    },
    {
        "id": 61,
        "question": "fox",
        "trueAnswer": "mouse",
        "falseAnswer": ["grapes", "avocado"]
    },
    {
        "id": 62,
        "question": "fox",
        "trueAnswer": "rabbit",
        "falseAnswer": ["chocolate", "garlic"]
    },
    {
        "id": 63,
        "question": "fox",
        "trueAnswer": "egg",
        "falseAnswer": ["tomato", "nuts"]
    },
    {
        "id": 64,
        "question": "fox",
        "trueAnswer": "strawberry",
        "falseAnswer": ["potato", "peach"]
    },
    {
        "id": 65,
        "question": "fox",
        "trueAnswer": "broccoli",
        "falseAnswer": ["mushroom", "eggplant"]
    },
    {
        "id": 66,
        "question": "lion",
        "trueAnswer": "gazelle",
        "falseAnswer": ["mushroom", "avocado"]
    },
    {
        "id": 67,
        "question": "lion",
        "trueAnswer": "chicken",
        "falseAnswer": ["bread", "chocolate"]
    },
    {
        "id": 68,
        "question": "lion",
        "trueAnswer": "deer",
        "falseAnswer": ["milk", "potato"]
    },
    {
        "id": 69,
        "question": "lion",
        "trueAnswer": "rabbit",
        "falseAnswer": ["grapes", "apple"]
    },
    {
        "id": 70,
        "question": "lion",
        "trueAnswer": "goat",
        "falseAnswer": ["eggplant", "carrot"]
    },
    {
        "id": 71,
        "question": "wolf",
        "trueAnswer": "moose",
        "falseAnswer": ["apple", "banana"]
    },
    {
        "id": 72,
        "question": "wolf",
        "trueAnswer": "rabbit",
        "falseAnswer": ["cucumber", "watermelon"]
    },
    {
        "id": 73,
        "question": "wolf",
        "trueAnswer": "deer",
        "falseAnswer": ["carrot", "peach"]
    },
    {
        "id": 74,
        "question": "wolf",
        "trueAnswer": "chicken",
        "falseAnswer": ["broccoli", "cabbage"]
    },
    {
        "id": 75,
        "question": "wolf",
        "trueAnswer": "duck",
        "falseAnswer": ["strawberry", "tomato"]
    },
    {
        "id": 76,
        "question": "bear",
        "trueAnswer": "fish",
        "falseAnswer": ["chocolate", "orange"]
    },
    {
        "id": 77,
        "question": "bear",
        "trueAnswer": "rabbit",
        "falseAnswer": ["avocado", "bread"]
    },
    {
        "id": 78,
        "question": "bear",
        "trueAnswer": "moose",
        "falseAnswer": ["onion", "milk"]
    },
    {
        "id": 79,
        "question": "bear",
        "trueAnswer": "apple",
        "falseAnswer": ["cheese", "garlic"]
    },
    {
        "id": 80,
        "question": "bear",
        "trueAnswer": "honey",
        "falseAnswer": ["cabbage", "hedgehog"]
    },
    {
        "id": 81,
        "question": "deer",
        "trueAnswer": "grass",
        "falseAnswer": ["meat", "orange"]
    },
    {
        "id": 82,
        "question": "deer",
        "trueAnswer": "apple",
        "falseAnswer": ["onion", "tomato"]
    },
    {
        "id": 83,
        "question": "deer",
        "trueAnswer": "mushroom",
        "falseAnswer": ["potato", "garlic"]
    },
    {
        "id": 84,
        "question": "deer",
        "trueAnswer": "nuts",
        "falseAnswer": ["eggplant", "cabbage"]
    },
    {
        "id": 85,
        "question": "deer",
        "trueAnswer": "carrot",
        "falseAnswer": ["avocado", "grapes"]
    },
    {
        "id": 86,
        "question": "antelope",
        "trueAnswer": "grass",
        "falseAnswer": ["orange", "eggplant"]
    },
    {
        "id": 87,
        "question": "antelope",
        "trueAnswer": "pear",
        "falseAnswer": ["chicken", "milk"]
    },
    {
        "id": 88,
        "question": "antelope",
        "trueAnswer": "carrot",
        "falseAnswer": ["cheese", "meat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 89,
        "question": "antelope",
        "trueAnswer": "cucumber",
        "falseAnswer": ["potato", "broccoli"]
    },
    {
        "id": 90,
        "question": "antelope",
        "trueAnswer": "pumpkin",
        "falseAnswer": ["avocado", "honey"]
    },
    {
        "id": 91,
        "question": "panda",
        "trueAnswer": "bamboo",
        "falseAnswer": ["gazelle", "orange"]
    },
    {
        "id": 92,
        "question": "panda",
        "trueAnswer": "apple",
        "falseAnswer": ["milk", "pineapple"]
    },
    {
        "id": 93,
        "question": "panda",
        "trueAnswer": "carrot",
        "falseAnswer": ["cheese", "chocolate"]
    },
    {
        "id": 94,
        "question": "panda",
        "trueAnswer": "watermelon",
        "falseAnswer": ["chicken", "tomato"]
    },
    {
        "id": 95,
        "question": "panda",
        "trueAnswer": "rice",
        "falseAnswer": ["onion", "fish"]
    },
    {
        "id": 96,
        "question": "giraffe",
        "trueAnswer": "leaves",
        "falseAnswer": ["meat", "milk"]
    },
    {
        "id": 97,
        "question": "giraffe",
        "trueAnswer": "apple",
        "falseAnswer": ["cheese", "orange"]
    },
    {
        "id": 98,
        "question": "giraffe",
        "trueAnswer": "pumpkin",
        "falseAnswer": ["pineapple", "chocolate"]
    },
    {
        "id": 99,
        "question": "giraffe",
        "trueAnswer": "carrot",
        "falseAnswer": ["fish", "eggplant"]
    },
    {
        "id": 100,
        "question": "giraffe",
        "trueAnswer": "cucumber",
        "falseAnswer": ["broccoli", "chicken"]
    },
    {
        "id": 101,
        "question": "monkey",
        "trueAnswer": "banana",
        "falseAnswer": ["eggplant", "avocado"]
    },
    {
        "id": 102,
        "question": "monkey",
        "trueAnswer": "apple",
        "falseAnswer": ["onion", "chocolate"]
    },
    {
        "id": 103,
        "question": "monkey",
        "trueAnswer": "grapes",
        "falseAnswer": ["garlic", "orange"]
    },
    {
        "id": 104,
        "question": "monkey",
        "trueAnswer": "carrot",
        "falseAnswer": ["potato", "fish"]
    },
    {
        "id": 105,
        "question": "monkey",
        "trueAnswer": "broccoli",
        "falseAnswer": ["milk", "tomato"]
    },
    {
        "id": 106,
        "question": "zebra",
        "trueAnswer": "grass",
        "falseAnswer": ["meat", "fish"]
    },
    {
        "id": 107,
        "question": "zebra",
        "trueAnswer": "pear",
        "falseAnswer": ["milk", "bread"]
    },
    {
        "id": 108,
        "question": "zebra",
        "trueAnswer": "carrot",
        "falseAnswer": ["cheese", "onion"]
    },
    {
        "id": 109,
        "question": "zebra",
        "trueAnswer": "strawberry",
        "falseAnswer": ["chocolate", "avocado"]
    },
    {
        "id": 110,
        "question": "zebra",
        "trueAnswer": "watermelon",
        "falseAnswer": ["garlic", "tomato"]
    },
    {
        "id": 111,
        "question": "tiger",
        "trueAnswer": "deer",
        "falseAnswer": ["apple", "banana"]
    },
    {
        "id": 112,
        "question": "tiger",
        "trueAnswer": "monkey",
        "falseAnswer": ["carrot", "bread"]
    },
    {
        "id": 113,
        "question": "tiger",
        "trueAnswer": "rabbit",
        "falseAnswer": ["watermelon", "cheese"]
    },
    {
        "id": 114,
        "question": "tiger",
        "trueAnswer": "goat",
        "falseAnswer": ["tomato", "grapes"]
    },
    {
        "id": 115,
        "question": "tiger",
        "trueAnswer": "chicken",
        "falseAnswer": ["cucumber", "pear"]
    },
    {
        "id": 116,
        "question": "leopard",
        "trueAnswer": "deer",
        "falseAnswer": ["apple", "banana"]
    },
    {
        "id": 117,
        "question": "leopard",
        "trueAnswer": "monkey",
        "falseAnswer": ["carrot", "bread"]
    },
    {
        "id": 118,
        "question": "leopard",
        "trueAnswer": "rabbit",
        "falseAnswer": ["watermelon", "cheese"]
    },
    {
        "id": 119,
        "question": "leopard",
        "trueAnswer": "goat",
        "falseAnswer": ["tomato", "grapes"]
    },
    {
        "id": 120,
        "question": "leopard",
        "trueAnswer": "mouse",
        "falseAnswer": ["cucumber", "pear"]
    },
    {
        "id": 121,
        "question": "elephant",
        "trueAnswer": "grass",
        "falseAnswer": ["deer", "chocolate"]
    },
    {
        "id": 122,
        "question": "elephant",
        "trueAnswer": "bamboo",
        "falseAnswer": ["bread", "egg"]
    },
    {
        "id": 123,
        "question": "elephant",
        "trueAnswer": "banana",
        "falseAnswer": ["chicken", "cheese"]
    },
    {
        "id": 124,
        "question": "elephant",
        "trueAnswer": "pumpkin",
        "falseAnswer": ["fish", "milk"]
    },
    {
        "id": 125,
        "question": "elephant",
        "trueAnswer": "corn",
        "falseAnswer": ["avocado", "orange"]
    },
    {
        "id": 126,
        "question": "hippopotamus",
        "trueAnswer": "grass",
        "falseAnswer": ["egg", "garlic"]
    },
    {
        "id": 127,
        "question": "hippopotamus",
        "trueAnswer": "hay",
        "falseAnswer": ["fish", "orange"]
    },
    {
        "id": 128,
        "question": "hippopotamus",
        "trueAnswer": "carrot",
        "falseAnswer": ["grapes", "milk"]
    },
    {
        "id": 129,
        "question": "hippopotamus",
        "trueAnswer": "watermelon",
        "falseAnswer": ["cheese", "chicken"]
    },
    {
        "id": 130,
        "question": "hippopotamus",
        "trueAnswer": "pumpkin",
        "falseAnswer": ["goat", "avocado"]
    },
    {
        "id": 131,
        "question": "camel",
        "trueAnswer": "grass",
        "falseAnswer": ["onion", "milk"]
    },
    {
        "id": 132,
        "question": "camel",
        "trueAnswer": "hay",
        "falseAnswer": ["garlic", "cheese"]
    },
    {
        "id": 133,
        "question": "camel",
        "trueAnswer": "corn",
        "falseAnswer": ["orange", "meat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 134,
        "question": "camel",
        "trueAnswer": "carrot",
        "falseAnswer": ["eggplant", "fish"]
    },
    {
        "id": 135,
        "question": "camel",
        "trueAnswer": "pumpkin",
        "falseAnswer": ["avocado", "deer"]
    },
    {
        "id": 136,
        "question": "rhinoceros",
        "trueAnswer": "grass",
        "falseAnswer": ["egg", "grapes"]
    },
    {
        "id": 137,
        "question": "rhinoceros",
        "trueAnswer": "hay",
        "falseAnswer": ["chicken", "garlic"]
    },
    {
        "id": 138,
        "question": "rhinoceros",
        "trueAnswer": "carrot",
        "falseAnswer": ["cheese", "orange"]
    },
    {
        "id": 139,
        "question": "rhinoceros",
        "trueAnswer": "pumpkin",
        "falseAnswer": ["chocolate", "garlic"]
    },
    {
        "id": 140,
        "question": "rhinoceros",
        "trueAnswer": "pear",
        "falseAnswer": ["bread", "deer"]
    },
    {
        "id": 141,
        "question": "hedgehog",
        "trueAnswer": "apple",
        "falseAnswer": ["milk", "bread"]
    },
    {
        "id": 142,
        "question": "hedgehog",
        "trueAnswer": "carrot",
        "falseAnswer": ["grapes", "meat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 143,
        "question": "hedgehog",
        "trueAnswer": "cucumber",
        "falseAnswer": ["nuts", "orange"]
    },
    {
        "id": 144,
        "question": "hedgehog",
        "trueAnswer": "strawberry",
        "falseAnswer": ["chocolate", "avocado"]
    },
    {
        "id": 145,
        "question": "hedgehog",
        "trueAnswer": "banana",
        "falseAnswer": ["onion", "chicken"]
    },
    {
        "id": 146,
        "question": "turtle",
        "trueAnswer": "carrot",
        "falseAnswer": ["milk", "bear"]
    },
    {
        "id": 147,
        "question": "turtle",
        "trueAnswer": "cucumber",
        "falseAnswer": ["cheese", "chocolate"]
    },
    {
        "id": 148,
        "question": "turtle",
        "trueAnswer": "strawberry",
        "falseAnswer": ["bread", "rabbit"]
    },
    {
        "id": 149,
        "question": "turtle",
        "trueAnswer": "hay",
        "falseAnswer": ["avocado", "chicken"]
    },
    {
        "id": 150,
        "question": "turtle",
        "trueAnswer": "apple",
        "falseAnswer": ["deer", "tomato"]
    },
    {
        "id": 151,
        "question": "beaver",
        "trueAnswer": "apple",
        "falseAnswer": ["fish", "milk"]
    },
    {
        "id": 152,
        "question": "beaver",
        "trueAnswer": "pear",
        "falseAnswer": ["cheese", "chicken"]
    },
    {
        "id": 153,
        "question": "beaver",
        "trueAnswer": "carrot",
        "falseAnswer": ["bread", "orange"]
    },
    {
        "id": 154,
        "question": "beaver",
        "trueAnswer": "potato",
        "falseAnswer": ["tomato", "rabbit"]
    },
    {
        "id": 155,
        "question": "beaver",
        "trueAnswer": "leaves",
        "falseAnswer": ["chocolate", "meat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 156,
        "question": "squirrel",
        "trueAnswer": "nuts",
        "falseAnswer": ["meat", "chocolate"]
    },
    {
        "id": 157,
        "question": "squirrel",
        "trueAnswer": "apple",
        "falseAnswer": ["onion", "fish"]
    },
    {
        "id": 158,
        "question": "squirrel",
        "trueAnswer": "pear",
        "falseAnswer": ["avocado", "bread"]
    },
    {
        "id": 159,
        "question": "squirrel",
        "trueAnswer": "corn",
        "falseAnswer": ["garlic", "potato"]
    },
    {
        "id": 160,
        "question": "squirrel",
        "trueAnswer": "grapes",
        "falseAnswer": ["milk", "cheese"]
    },
    {
        "id": 161,
        "question": "gazelle",
        "trueAnswer": "grass",
        "falseAnswer": ["orange", "eggplant"]
    },
    {
        "id": 162,
        "question": "gazelle",
        "trueAnswer": "pear",
        "falseAnswer": ["chicken", "milk"]
    },
    {
        "id": 163,
        "question": "gazelle",
        "trueAnswer": "carrot",
        "falseAnswer": ["cheese", "meat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 164,
        "question": "gazelle",
        "trueAnswer": "cucumber",
        "falseAnswer": ["potato", "broccoli"]
    },
    {
        "id": 165,
        "question": "gazelle",
        "trueAnswer": "pumpkin",
        "falseAnswer": ["avocado", "honey"]
    },
    {
        "id": 166,
        "question": "badger",
        "trueAnswer": "cherry",
        "falseAnswer": ["pineapple", "onion"]
    },
    {
        "id": 167,
        "question": "badger",
        "trueAnswer": "carrot",
        "falseAnswer": ["orange", "garlic"]
    },
    {
        "id": 168,
        "question": "badger",
        "trueAnswer": "mushroom",
        "falseAnswer": ["avocado", "rabbit"]
    },
    {
        "id": 169,
        "question": "badger",
        "trueAnswer": "pumpkin",
        "falseAnswer": ["potato", "deer"]
    },
    {
        "id": 170,
        "question": "badger",
        "trueAnswer": "apple",
        "falseAnswer": ["eggplant", "tomato"]
    },
    {
        "id": 171,
        "question": "jackal",
        "trueAnswer": "rabbit",
        "falseAnswer": ["orange", "broccoli"]
    },
    {
        "id": 172,
        "question": "jackal",
        "trueAnswer": "fish",
        "falseAnswer": ["avocado", "eggplant"]
    },
    {
        "id": 173,
        "question": "jackal",
        "trueAnswer": "goat",
        "falseAnswer": ["grapes", "potato"]
    },
    {
        "id": 174,
        "question": "jackal",
        "trueAnswer": "apple",
        "falseAnswer": ["pineapple", "garlic"]
    },
    {
        "id": 175,
        "question": "jackal",
        "trueAnswer": "pumpkin",
        "falseAnswer": ["onion", "chocolate"]
    },
    {
        "id": 176,
        "question": "llama",
        "trueAnswer": "grass",
        "falseAnswer": ["pineapple", "bread"]
    },
    {
        "id": 177,
        "question": "llama",
        "trueAnswer": "hay",
        "falseAnswer": ["avocado", "chocolate"]
    },
    {
        "id": 178,
        "question": "llama",
        "trueAnswer": "apple",
        "falseAnswer": ["eggplant", "rabbit"]
    },
    {
        "id": 179,
        "question": "llama",
        "trueAnswer": "carrot",
        "falseAnswer": ["goat", "cheese"]
    },
    {
        "id": 180,
        "question": "llama",
        "trueAnswer": "pumpkin",
        "falseAnswer": ["deer", "milk"]
    },
    {
        "id": 181,
        "question": "mouse",
        "trueAnswer": "strawberry",
        "falseAnswer": ["onion", "rabbit"]
    },
    {
        "id": 182,
        "question": "mouse",
        "trueAnswer": "broccoli",
        "falseAnswer": ["garlic", "cat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 183,
        "question": "mouse",
        "trueAnswer": "cucumber",
        "falseAnswer": ["avocado", "tomato"]
    },
    {
        "id": 184,
        "question": "mouse",
        "trueAnswer": "nuts",
        "falseAnswer": ["chocolate", "mushroom"]
    },
    {
        "id": 185,
        "question": "mouse",
        "trueAnswer": "pear",
        "falseAnswer": ["deer", "orange"]
    },
    {
        "id": 186,
        "question": "kangaroo",
        "trueAnswer": "grass",
        "falseAnswer": ["bread", "cabbage"]
    },
    {
        "id": 187,
        "question": "kangaroo",
        "trueAnswer": "apple",
        "falseAnswer": ["chocolate", "grapes"]
    },
    {
        "id": 188,
        "question": "kangaroo",
        "trueAnswer": "carrot",
        "falseAnswer": ["orange", "onion"]
    },
    {
        "id": 189,
        "question": "kangaroo",
        "trueAnswer": "pumpkin",
        "falseAnswer": ["eggplant", "garlic"]
    },
    {
        "id": 190,
        "question": "kangaroo",
        "trueAnswer": "banana",
        "falseAnswer": ["avocado", "tomato"]
    },
    {
        "id": 191,
        "question": "meerkat",
        "trueAnswer": "egg",
        "falseAnswer": ["bread", "goat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 192,
        "question": "meerkat",
        "trueAnswer": "snake",
        "falseAnswer": ["chocolate", "onion"]
    },
    {
        "id": 193,
        "question": "meerkat",
        "trueAnswer": "apple",
        "falseAnswer": ["cheese", "garlic"]
    },
    {
        "id": 194,
        "question": "meerkat",
        "trueAnswer": "carrot",
        "falseAnswer": ["eggplant", "orange"]
    },
    {
        "id": 195,
        "question": "meerkat",
        "trueAnswer": "pumpkin",
        "falseAnswer": ["avocado", "potato"]
    },
    {
        "id": 196,
        "question": "crocodile",
        "trueAnswer": "fish",
        "falseAnswer": ["apple", "bread"]
    },
    {
        "id": 197,
        "question": "crocodile",
        "trueAnswer": "frog",
        "falseAnswer": ["banana", "watermelon"]
    },
    {
        "id": 198,
        "question": "crocodile",
        "trueAnswer": "turtle",
        "falseAnswer": ["carrot", "broccoli"]
    },
    {
        "id": 199,
        "question": "crocodile",
        "trueAnswer": "rabbit",
        "falseAnswer": ["corn", "tomato"]
    },
    {
        "id": 200,
        "question": "crocodile",
        "trueAnswer": "deer",
        "falseAnswer": ["mushroom", "orange"]
    },
    {
        "id": 201,
        "question": "apple",
        "trueAnswer": "pig",
        "falseAnswer": ["crocodile", "snake"]
    },
    {
        "id": 202,
        "question": "apple",
        "trueAnswer": "rabbit",
        "falseAnswer": ["wolf", "fox"]
    },
    {
        "id": 203,
        "question": "apple",
        "trueAnswer": "bear",
        "falseAnswer": ["fish", "lion"]
    },
    {
        "id": 204,
        "question": "apple",
        "trueAnswer": "panda",
        "falseAnswer": ["tiger", "leopard"]
    },
    {
        "id": 205,
        "question": "banana",
        "trueAnswer": "monkey",
        "falseAnswer": ["lion", "tiger"]
    },
    {
        "id": 206,
        "question": "banana",
        "trueAnswer": "elephant",
        "falseAnswer": ["wolf", "leopard"]
    },
    {
        "id": 207,
        "question": "banana",
        "trueAnswer": "rabbit",
        "falseAnswer": ["crocodile", "snake"]
    },
    {
        "id": 208,
        "question": "bamboo",
        "trueAnswer": "elephant",
        "falseAnswer": ["cat", "rabbit"]
    },
    {
        "id": 209,
        "question": "bamboo",
        "trueAnswer": "panda",
        "falseAnswer": ["deer", "goat"]
    },
    {
        "id": 210,
        "question": "broccoli",
        "trueAnswer": "fox",
        "falseAnswer": ["pig", "wolf"]
    },
    {
        "id": 211,
        "question": "broccoli",
        "trueAnswer": "monkey",
        "falseAnswer": ["horse", "giraffe"]
    },
    {
        "id": 212,
        "question": "broccoli",
        "trueAnswer": "mouse",
        "falseAnswer": ["antelope", "jackal"]
    },
    {
        "id": 213,
        "question": "cabbage",
        "trueAnswer": "pig",
        "falseAnswer": ["bear", "deer"]
    },
    {
        "id": 214,
        "question": "cabbage",
        "trueAnswer": "rabbit",
        "falseAnswer": ["kangaroo", "wolf"]
    },
    {
        "id": 215,
        "question": "cabbage",
        "trueAnswer": "chicken",
        "falseAnswer": ["lion", "cow"]
    },
    {
        "id": 216,
        "question": "cabbage",
        "trueAnswer": "duck",
        "falseAnswer": ["wolf", "deer"]
    },
    {
        "id": 217,
        "question": "cabbage",
        "trueAnswer": "goat",
        "falseAnswer": ["tiger", "bear"]
    },
    {
        "id": 218,
        "question": "carrot",
        "trueAnswer": "antelope",
        "falseAnswer": ["wolf", "snake"]
    },
    {
        "id": 219,
        "question": "carrot",
        "trueAnswer": "llama",
        "falseAnswer": ["lion", "crocodile"]
    },
    {
        "id": 220,
        "question": "carrot",
        "trueAnswer": "badger",
        "falseAnswer": ["tiger", "leopard"]
    },
    {
        "id": 221,
        "question": "corn",
        "trueAnswer": "squirrel",
        "falseAnswer": ["tiger", "leopard"]
    },
    {
        "id": 222,
        "question": "cherry",
        "trueAnswer": "badger",
        "falseAnswer": ["cow", "sheep"]
    },
    {
        "id": 223,
        "question": "corn",
        "trueAnswer": "pig",
        "falseAnswer": ["crocodile", "snake"]
    },
    {
        "id": 224,
        "question": "corn",
        "trueAnswer": "chicken",
        "falseAnswer": ["lion", "wolf"]
    },
    {
        "id": 225,
        "question": "corn",
        "trueAnswer": "duck",
        "falseAnswer": ["leopard", "panda"]
    },
    {
        "id": 226,
        "question": "corn",
        "trueAnswer": "camel",
        "falseAnswer": ["tiger", "fish"]
    },
    {
        "id": 227,
        "question": "cucumber",
        "trueAnswer": "horse",
        "falseAnswer": ["wolf", "tiger"]
    },
    {
        "id": 228,
        "question": "cucumber",
        "trueAnswer": "giraffe",
        "falseAnswer": ["leopard", "fish"]
    },
    {
        "id": 229,
        "question": "cucumber",
        "trueAnswer": "duck",
        "falseAnswer": ["crocodile", "snake"]
    },
    {
        "id": 230,
        "question": "watermelon",
        "trueAnswer": "cow",
        "falseAnswer": ["lion", "leopard"]
    },
    {
        "id": 231,
        "question": "egg",
        "trueAnswer": "dog",
        "falseAnswer": ["hippopotamus", "elephant"]
    },{
        "id": 232,
        "question": "egg",
        "trueAnswer": "fox",
        "falseAnswer": ["rhinoceros", "deer"]
    },
    {
        "id": 233,
        "question": "egg",
        "trueAnswer": "meerkat",
        "falseAnswer": ["giraffe", "zebra"]
    },{
        "id": 234,
        "question": "grass",
        "trueAnswer": "elephant",
        "falseAnswer": ["fish", "monkey"]
    },{
        "id": 235,
        "question": "grass",
        "trueAnswer": "hippopotamus",
        "falseAnswer": ["lion", "leopard"]
    },{
        "id": 236,
        "question": "grass",
        "trueAnswer": "camel",
        "falseAnswer": ["fox", "leopard"]
    },{
        "id": 237,
        "question": "grass",
        "trueAnswer": "rhinoceros",
        "falseAnswer": ["wolf", "crocodile"]
    },{
        "id": 238,
        "question": "grass",
        "trueAnswer": "gazelle",
        "falseAnswer": ["panda", "tiger"]
    },{
        "id": 239,
        "question": "grapes",
        "trueAnswer": "squirrel",
        "falseAnswer": ["jackal", "kangaroo"]
    },{
        "id": 240,
        "question": "hay",
        "trueAnswer": "goat",
        "falseAnswer": ["crocodile", "leopard"]
    },{
        "id": 241,
        "question": "hay",
        "trueAnswer": "hippopotamus",
        "falseAnswer": ["tiger", "monkey"]
    },
    {
        "id": 242,
        "question": "hay",
        "trueAnswer": "camel",
        "falseAnswer": ["panda", "wolf"]
    },
    {
        "id": 243,
        "question": "hay",
        "trueAnswer": "rhinoceros",
        "falseAnswer": ["lion", "fox"]
    },
    {
        "id": 244,
        "question": "meat",
        "trueAnswer": "cat",
        "falseAnswer": ["deer", "sheep"]
    },
    {
        "id": 245,
        "question": "meat",
        "trueAnswer": "wolf",
        "falseAnswer": ["panda", "giraffe"]
    },
    {
        "id": 246,
        "question": "meat",
        "trueAnswer": "lion",
        "falseAnswer": ["zebra", "elephant"]
    },
    {
        "id": 247,
        "question": "meat",
        "trueAnswer": "tiger",
        "falseAnswer": ["hippopotamus", "llama"]
    },
    {
        "id": 248,
        "question": "meat",
        "trueAnswer": "crocodile",
        "falseAnswer": ["horse", "donkey"]
    },
    {
        "id": 249,
        "question": "mushroom",
        "trueAnswer": "deer",
        "falseAnswer": ["crocodile", "fox"]
    },
    {
        "id": 250,
        "question": "mushroom",
        "trueAnswer": "badger",
        "falseAnswer": ["lion", "mouse"]
    },
    {
        "id": 51,
        "question": "nuts",
        "trueAnswer": "mouse",
        "falseAnswer": ["sheep", "hedgehog"]
    },
    {
        "id": 252,
        "question": "nuts",
        "trueAnswer": "deer",
        "falseAnswer": ["cow", "goose"]
    },
    {
        "id": 253,
        "question": "nuts",
        "trueAnswer": "squirrel",
        "falseAnswer": ["pig", "fox"]
    },
    {
        "id": 254,
        "question": "pear",
        "trueAnswer": "antelope",
        "falseAnswer": ["leopard", "tiger"]
    },
    {
        "id": 255,
        "question": "pear",
        "trueAnswer": "zebra",
        "falseAnswer": ["crocodile", "lion"]
    },
    {
        "id": 256,
        "question": "pear",
        "trueAnswer": "rhinoceros",
        "falseAnswer": ["fish", "wolf"]
    },
    {
        "id": 257,
        "question": "pear",
        "trueAnswer": "beaver",
        "falseAnswer": ["panda", "snake"]
    },
    {
        "id": 258,
        "question": "potato",
        "trueAnswer": "beaver",
        "falseAnswer": ["deer", "monkey"]
    },
    {
        "id": 259,
        "question": "pumpkin",
        "trueAnswer": "hippopotamus",
        "falseAnswer": ["panda", "fish"]
    },
    {
        "id": 260,
        "question": "pumpkin",
        "trueAnswer": "camel",
        "falseAnswer": ["crocodile", "tiger"]
    },
    {
        "id": 261,
        "question": "pumpkin",
        "trueAnswer": "rhinoceros",
        "falseAnswer": ["lion", "wolf"]
    },
    {
        "id": 262,
        "question": "rice",
        "trueAnswer": "dog",
        "falseAnswer": ["zebra", "lion"]
    },
    {
        "id": 263,
        "question": "rice",
        "trueAnswer": "panda",
        "falseAnswer": ["elephant", "gazelle"]
    },
    {
        "id": 264,
        "question": "rice",
        "trueAnswer": "duck",
        "falseAnswer": ["wolf", "giraffe"]
    },
    {
        "id": 265,
        "question": "strawberry",
        "trueAnswer": "fox",
        "falseAnswer": ["crocodile", "snake"]
    },
    {
        "id": 266,
        "question": "strawberry",
        "trueAnswer": "zebra",
        "falseAnswer": ["panda", "wolf"]
    },
    {
        "id": 267,
        "question": "strawberry",
        "trueAnswer": "rabbit",
        "falseAnswer": ["lion", "tiger"]
    },
    {
        "id": 268,
        "question": "watermelon",
        "trueAnswer": "zebra",
        "falseAnswer": ["panda", "fish"]
    },
    {
        "id": 269,
        "question": "watermelon",
        "trueAnswer": "hippopotamus",
        "falseAnswer": ["wolf", "snake"]
    }
]
